세상에, 청소했구나?
이 바닥 좀 봐!
Oh, my God, you cleaned!
Look at these floors!
몇 달간 부탁했는데
이제야 끝냈구나
You did the windows! I have been begging
you for months! And you did, you cleaned.
- 잔소리가 효과가 있었군
- 사실, 내가 한 게 아니야
-And nagging works!
-No, I didn't actually do this.
이런, 내가 또 자면서
청소한 거야?
Oh, no. Was I cleaning
in my sleep again?
네가 한 게 아니야
No, it wasn't you.
- 그럼, 누구야?
- 파출부를 구했어
-Well, then, who?
-I got a maid. Yay!
"아가씨"겠지
다른 여자였다면...
I hope by "maid" you mean "mistress"
because if some other woman was cleaning..
그래, 네 권리권을 이양해서
서운하겠지
Now, honey, I know you don't like
to relinquish control.
이양하단 말은
빼앗긴단 말의 포장이야
"Relinquish" is just a fancy word
for "lose."
좋은 사람이야, 네가 스펀지를
두는 방식을 칭찬했다고
She's nice, and she mentioned that she
adored the way you arranged the sponges.
사실이야?
Did she really say that?
응, 나도 믿기지 않아서
확실히 기억했거든
Yes, I distinctly remember because
I thought it was a joke.
- 그러니, 기회를 줘
- 그렇게 할게
-Now, just give her a chance, okay?
-Fine, I can do it.
- 왜 그래?
- 난 불안하면 청소를 해
-What's the matter?
-Usually when I'm this anxious, I clean.
프렌즈 시즌 8
'청바지 도둑'
어디를 가든 전화소리 때문에
짜증난다니까
Whose cell phone is that?
It's just so annoying. Everywhere you go.
네 가방에서 들려
I think it's coming from your bag.
그럴 리가 없는데
I never get calls!
여보세요?
Hello?
할로윈 파티 때 만난 에릭이에요
우술라의 약혼자요
Hi, it's Eric, from the Halloween
party. Ursula's fiance.
에릭, 안녕하세요?
내 번호를 어떻게 알았어요?
Oh, my God, Eric, hi!
Wait, how'd you get this number?
친구 중에 경찰이 있어서
알아낼 수 있죠
I have a friend who's a cop,
and he got it for me.
대단한 위법행위군요
그리고 참 뜻밖이에요
Wow. What an incredible violation
and wonderful surprise!
최근 우술라와 헤어졌는데
알려주고 싶었어요
Listen, I just.. I thought you should know
I broke up with Ursula.
그래요? 결국 했데!
Oh, you did?
He did it, he did it!
- 뭘?
- 조용히 해!
-What did he do?
-I'm talking!
궁금한 게 있어서 전화했어요
혹시 점심을 먹고 사는지요
Anyway, I was wondering if you were
the sort of person who eats lunch?
데이트 신청인가요?
Are you asking me out?
언니와 헤어졌다며
이런 일은 의외군요
Because it'd be kind of weird since you
just broke up with my sister.
그렇군요, 미안해요
안녕
Yeah, okay. I'm sorry. Bye.
잠시만요! 전 그냥
예의상 한 말이에요
No, no. Wait! I was just saying that
so you'd think I was a good person.
밀어붙여요
Fight for me.
거절은 받아들이지 않겠어요
I won't take "no" for an answer.
점심 먹으면서 상의해요
Not great, but we can work on it at lunch.
2시간 안에
당신 집으로 갈게요
I can be at your apartment
in two hours.
우리 집을 어떻게 알아요?
Great. How do you know where I live?
친구들이 있어요
I've got friends too.
이따 봐요
Okay, bye.
에릭과 데이트하기로 했어!
Oh, my God, I'm going out with Eric!
오늘은 생각보다
즐거운 하루가 되겠어
This day is really gonna be so much better
than I thought it was gonna be.
로스, 점심을 같이 못 먹겠어
Oh, Ross, I can't make lunch.
점심 먹을 시간이 생겼어
So apparently I'm available
for lunch.
나도 집을 알아봐야 해
I can't. I'm busy.
I'm apartment hunting.
이사 가려고?
You're moving?
아이가 태어나면
조이와 살 수 없잖아
I can't live with Joey
once the baby comes.
내 아기가 조이 말투를
배우면 곤란하잖아
I don't want my child's first words
to be, "How you doing?"
조이도 알고 있어?
So does Joey know you're moving?
말해주면 기뻐할 거야
I haven't discussed it with him,
but I know he'll be relieved.
지난주, 조이의 여자친구에게
입덧 얘기를 했어
Last week, he brought this girl over,
and I talked to her about morning sickness.
임산부 사진도 보여줬어
Then I showed her pictures
from my pregnancy book.
- 야하진 않겠지?
- 별로
-That's not really porn?
-Not so much.
오늘 아침에 들었는데
우리 건물에서 여자가 죽었대
I heard in the elevator this morning
that a woman in my building died.
나이 많은 여자야?
경치가 좋은 집에 살았대?
Oh, my God. Was she old?
Does she have a view?
서로 같은 건물에 살면
정말 좋을 것 같아
I don't know, but how great would that be?
You living in my building?
내가 아기도 보고
너희 집에 놀러가고
I could take care of the baby,
I could come over whenever I want..
네 허락 하에 말야
with your permission.
그러면 정말 좋을 거야
방을 볼 수 있을까?
That really would be great.
Well, can we see it?
오늘 아침 죽었다면
좀 무례하잖아
Maybe we shouldn't.
I mean, if she just died this morning.
맞아, 네 말도 일리가 있어
Yeah. No. No, you're right.
- 갈까?
- 그래
-Shall we?
-Yeah.
누구세요?
Yes?
전 이 건물 주민인
로스 겔러라고 해요
Hi. I'm Ross Geller.
I live in the building.
전 이 건물을 찬미하는
레이첼이라고 해요
And I'm Rachel,
an admirer of the building.
버호벤 부인께서
사망했단 소식을 들었어요
I heard about Mrs. Verhoeven passing
away, and I am so sorry for your loss.
- 돌아가시지 않았어요
- 뭐라고요?
-She didn't pass away.
-What?
- 어머닌 살아 계시다고요
- 하느님, 감사합니다
-My mother's still alive.
-Oh, thank God!
아침엔 굉장히 위독하셨지만
잘 견디고 계시죠
It looked like we were gonna lose her
this morning, but she's a tough old bird.
어머니랑 가까우신가요?
Are you close with her?
그럼요, 세탁실에서 만나면
Of course. She and I would
talk all the time..
대화를 많이 나눴어요
in the laundry room.
네덜란드어를 하세요?
You speak Dutch?
하긴 하지만
매우 고통스럽죠
You know, I would,
but it's just too painful.
아직 살아 계시단 거죠?
So she's really not dead.
네, 아직 버티고 계세요
No. She's hanging in there.
침실이 몇 개 있는 집에서
버티고 계신가요?
Could you tell me, is she hanging in
in a one-bedroom or a two?
빙 부인, 세제가 괜찮은데
어디서 팔아요?
Mrs. Bing, this tile cleaner is incredible.
Where did you get it?
내가 직접 만들어서 써요
Oh, well..
I make it myself.
암모니아와 레몬주스를
2대1 비율로 섞고, 비결은...
It's two parts ammonia and one part
lemon juice. The secret ingredient is..
우린 방금 만났어요
You know what? We just met.
이제 세탁실에 가서
빨래를 찾아올게요
Okay. I'm gonna go get the clothes
from the laundry room now.
냉장고 뒤는 갔다와서
청소할게요
When I come back,
I'll clean behind the refrigerator.
마음에 들어
I love her.
후딱 다녀올게요
I'll be back in a minute.
그래요
Okay.
- 내 말이 맞지?
- 내 청바지를 훔쳤어
-See? I told you.
-She stole my jeans!
뭐?
What?
내가 잃어버렸는데
입고 있어
I've been looking for them all week,
and she is wearing them.
훔친 청바지를 주인 앞에서
입고 있다고?
So she stole your pants and then
came back and wore them in front of you?
이건 완전범죄라고
Don't you see?
It's the perfect crime!
수년간 이 범행을
모의해 왔을 거야
She must have been
planning this for years!
내가 증명해 주지
I'll prove it to you, okay.
내가 펜을 떨어뜨려서
사타구니에 잉크가 묻었어
I dropped a pen in my lap, and it left
an ink stain on the crotch.
그 여자가 돌아오면
잉크자국을 보여주지
When she comes back, I will find it
and show you that stain!
청바지 회사에서 바지를 한 벌만
생산하진 않겠지?
Isn't it possible the company that sold
the jeans made more than just the one pair?
아마도
I guess.
자국을 확인하기 전 까진
의심하지 말자고
Shouldn't we give her the benefit of the
doubt before we snoop around her crotch?
알았어, 조합 비결을
말할 뻔했는데, 다행이군
Fine. I'm just glad I didn't give
her my secret ingredient.
비결이란 게 뭐야?
Out of curiosity,
what is your secret ingredient?
안 말해줘
Yeah.
- 안녕하세요?
- 들어와요, 반가워요
-Hi.
-Come in. I'm so glad you're here.
저도요
Yeah. Me too.
그렇지만 당신처럼
화난 상태는 아니에요
Not in the shaky, angry way
that you are, though.
미안해요, 우술라에게
약혼반지를 돌려 받고 왔어요
Sorry. I just saw Ursula.
I had to get the engagement ring back.
우술라 얼굴을 보니
전부 떠오르더라고요
Just seeing her brought it all back.
내게 말한 거짓말들
날 이용한 일들
All the lies, the way she used me.
그녀의 얼굴만 봐도
화가..
I just.. I get so angry,
just looking at her..
- 치밀더군요
- 맞아요
-Face.
-Yeah. Yeah.
미안해요, 당신을 쳐다보면
I'm sorry. It's just,
when I look at you..
우술라가 떠올라요
I see her.
그녀의 얼굴이 떠오르면서
조금 화가 나죠
And when I see her,
I get a little bit angry.
어디로 갈까요?
So where do you wanna eat?
당신이 싫어서가 아니에요
Not that I'm not enjoying
watching you flip out.
미안해요
Sorry.
- 상황이 안 좋군요
- 기다려요
-Maybe this is too weird.
-Wait.
당신을 쳐다볼 때
문제가 생기니까
There's only a problem
when I look at you.
방법이 있어요
I got it. I got it.
눈을 뽑으면 어떡해요?
No, don't tear out your eyes!
- 렌즈를 빼려고 했어요
- 다시 해 봐요
-I was just gonna take out my lenses.
-Oh, yeah. Try that.
이제 좀 나아요?
So is that better?
별로
Not really.
흐리게 보이긴 하지만
아직도 우술라로 보여요
You're blurry, but you still
look like Ursula. You're "Blursula."
잠시만요, 어쩌면...
Okay, wait. Maybe..
잠시 동안 당신을
안 쳐다보면 되겠군요
If I just don't look at you
for a while.
효과가 있어요, 화가 안 나요
정말 멋진 데이트예요
See? It works. I'm not angry at
all anymore. This is a great date!
별로예요
Yeah, not so much.
대화가 힘들잖아요
It's kind of hard
to have a conversation.
대화가 가능해요
Oh, no.
Sure, we can have a conversation.
당신 얘기 좀 해줘요
Tell me a little
something about yourself.
나요?
Oh, me?
에릭, 이쪽으로 돌아서요
Look, Eric, turn around.
이래서야 되겠어요?
우리의 첫 데이트잖아요
I like you, but it shouldn't be
this hard. This is our first date.
첫 데이트는 설레고
전기도 흐르고
First dates are supposed to be
about excitement and electricity and..
내 손을 일부러 건드렸을까
생각도 하고, 첫 키스를 하고
"He just touched my hand,
did he mean to?" and first kisses..
두 번째 키스를 하죠
Second kisses.
커피 고마워, 또는...
Thanks for the coffee, or:
대화 끝났어
Yeah, we're done.
로스, 조류에 관한 아이맥스
영화 보러 갈까?
Hey, Ross. You wanna go see
that new lMAX movie on tide pools?
- 정말?
- 아니
-Really?
-No.
하지만 닉스 경기표가 있어
But I got Knicks tickets
for you, me and Chandler.
멋져!
Sweet!
스트립 클럽도 가자
And then afterwards,
we can go to a strip joint.
- 정말?
- 아니
-Really?
-No.
가자
All right, let's go.
난 집에 들러야 돼
I have to stop by my place.
경기를 녹화하려고?
그래도 TV엔 안 나온다니까
To tape the game? You do this every
time. You're not gonna be on TV!
집이 나왔는지 보려고
No, I have to see if this apartment
became available.
- 이사 가려고?
- 내가 아니고 레이첼이야
-You're switching apartments?
-It's not for me, it's for Rachel.
- 레이첼은 집이 있잖아
- 아기를 낳으면 옮길 거래
-She has an apartment.
-When the baby comes, she's gonna move.
- 그래?
- 응
-She is?
-Yeah.
아기랑 같이 살 거라고
생각하진 않았지?
You didn't expect her
to live there with the baby?
생각도 안 했어
I didn't really think about it.
건터, 넌 에이즐이야
Hey, Gunther, you're an ezel.
망할!
Damn it!
- 바지가 멋져요
- 고마워요
-Nice jeans.
-Oh, thanks.
- 상의가 마음에 들어요
- 이건 안 돼요
-I like your top.
-Oh. You're not getting it.
- 무슨 일이에요?
- 깜빡 잠이 들었어요
-What happened?
-Oh. I fell asleep!
점심 먹을까 하는데요
I was thinking about taking
my lunch break.
찬장 위를 닦아 줄래요?
그럼, 식욕이 날 거예요
Will you do the top of the cabinets?
That'll work up your appetite for lunch.
알았어요
All right.
안녕하세요?
Hello.
왜 그래요?
What's going on?
파출부를 처음 써 봐요
이러면 안 되나요?
I'm sorry. I've never had a maid
before. Is this not okay?
이해가 안 돼요
I don't understand.
왜 머리를 갖다댔어요?
Why was your head
just between my legs?
당연히 궁금하겠죠
That's a fair question.
내가 그런 이유는...
Well, my head was
between your legs..
당신이 매력적으로 보여서
그랬어요
because I find you
very attractive.
꼬시는 거예요?
Are you coming onto me?
맞아요
Apparently.
- 안녕
-Hey.
- 경기는 어땠어?
- 괜찮았는데, 너무 과식했어
-How was the game?
-It was okay. I ate way too much.
로스에게 들었는데
집을 구한다며?
I was talking to Ross, and he said
you were looking for a new place.
네덜란드 사람이 그만 버티면
건너편으로 옮길 거야
Yeah. Hopefully across the street.
If certain Dutch people would just let go.
이사가지 말았으면 좋겠어
I was kind of hoping you'd stay.
조이, 아기를 낳으면
집이 좁을 거야
Joey, I have to go.
There's no room for a baby here.
집이 좁다니?
아기는 이만하잖아
No room? It's a baby.
It's, like, this big.
그냥 여기에 두면 되잖아
You could put it over here.
아니면, 여기도 괜찮고
그렇지?
Or we could put it right here.
It's cute, right?
이곳에 두면
있는지도 모를 거라고
Or put it over here.
You wouldn't even notice it.
"아기가 어디 있지?"
"아, 여기 있군"
"Where's the baby?"
"Oh, it's right over.."
아기를 어디에 두는 지가
문제가 아니야
Honey, it's not just a matter
of where you put it.
모든게 바뀌게 돼
하루종일 울어댄다고
A baby changes everything.
They cry all the time.
네가 여자를 데려와
꼬시기도 힘들잖아
Imagine bringing home some girl and
trying to score with a screaming baby.
새로운 도전일 거야
그리 어렵지 않아
I could use a challenge.
It's getting pretty easy.
네 마음은 고맙지만
나도 어쩔 수 없어
It's so sweet that you want me
to stay, but I can't.
네 일거수일투족에
지장이 생길 거라고
It would disrupt your entire life.
난 그냥...
너와 사는 게 좋아서 그래
It's just..
I love living with you so much.
- 난 변화를 바라지 않아
- 알아
-I wish things didn't have to change.
-I know.
이게 전부 로스 탓이야
You know, I blame Ross for this.
나도 조금은 공감해
I do too, a little bit.
네가 보고 싶을 거야
I'm gonna miss you.
가장 섹시한 룸메이트였어
You're the hottest roommate
I ever had.
난 가봐야 해요
안마 예약이 있어요
Oh, no, I have to go.
I have a massage appointment.
가지 말고 계속해요
내가 계산할게요
No, stay here. We'll keep doing this.
I'll pay you.
안 돼요, 전에도 그러다
혼났어요
No, I've gotten in trouble
for that before.
- 이따 볼까요?
- 그럼요
-I'll see you later?
-Absolutely.
당신의 키스가 좋아요
I love the way you kiss.
정말이에요? 키스는
내가 제일 못하는 거예요
Really? That's the thing I'm worst at!
You'll see.
안녕
Hey.
- 브렌다의 급여를 올려야겠어
- 왜?
-Hey. I think Brenda needs a raise.
-How come?
내가 사타구니에
머리를 들이댔어
Because I put my head
between her legs.
- 그 여자의 바지 때문에?
- 내 바지라고!
-To see her pants?
-They're my pants!
잉크 자국이 있어?
Are you sure?
Did you see the stain?
머리를 갖다대니까
어두워서 안 보였어
No. I was getting into position,
and then everything went dark.
그 여자는 도둑이 아니니까
이제 그만둬
She is not stealing from us, okay.
Will you let this go?
알았어
Fine.
- 그 여자가 내 브라를 찼어
- 세상에
-She's wearing my bra!
-Oh, dear God!
끈을 보니 확실히 알겠어
My pink, flowered bra!
I recognize the strap!
네가 미쳤단 사실은
아직 모르겠어?
Yet you don't recognize
that you're crazy?
이건 어때?
내가 가면 브라를 확인해
Here's the plan. I'm going to leave,
and you're gonna look at Brenda's bra.
이건 어때? 싫어!
Here's another plan. No.
그녀는 내가 자기를
좋아하는 줄 알아
I would do it, but she thinks
I'm attracted to her.
- 왜?
- 머리 얘기 못 들었어?
-Why?
-Did you not hear where my head was?
우린 같은 편이라고
We're a team.
We're in this together.
배심원도 그렇게 볼까 봐
두렵군
I fear a jury will see it
the same way.
날 위해서 해 줘
평소에도 잘 훔쳐보잖아
Do this for me. I catch you looking
at women's breasts all the time.
알고 있었어?
You see that?
이게 보여?
Do you see this?
알겠어, 이해해
All right, yes.
Okay. I get your point.
네 브라가 맞아도
내쫓지마
But if it's not her bra, will you
just let the woman clean?
찢겨진 오른쪽 컵을 보면
내 브라인지 알 거야
Yes. You'll know it's mine because on
the right cup, there's a very noticeable rip.
새로 사지 그래?
You need new clothes.
- 좀 어떠신가요?
- 안 좋아 보여요
-Hi. How is she?
-It's not looking good.
블로멘을 좀 사왔어요
Well, I brought her some bloemen.
고마워요, 인사 드릴래요?
모친께 의미가 클 거예요
That's so sweet. Would you like to say
goodbye? It would mean a lot to her.
그럴 것 같지 않은데요
Oh, I don't know that it would.
- 별로 기억하지 못하세요
- 알았어요
-Well, her memory is pretty much gone.
-All right, then.
- 왔군요
- 어서 와요
-Hey!
-Welcome back.
- 하던 일 계속 할까요?
- 아직도 힘이 빠져있어요
-Shall we pick up from where we left off?
-I'm still tired from this afternoon.
- 왜요?
- 섹스 때문예요
-Why?
-The sex.
- 무슨 섹스?
- 우리가 나눈 섹스요
-What sex?
-Our sex.
우리가 언제요?
We didn't have sex.
그게 당신이 아니었다면
당신과 닮은...
If I didn't have sex with you, I had sex
with somebody that looked like..
- 우술라와?
- 조금
-You had sex with Ursula?
-A little bit.
당신인 줄 알고
내가 키스한 후...
She walked in, I thought she was you
and I kissed her and..
- 옷이 다르잖아요
- 당신을 만나 흥분했어요
-You didn't notice different clothes?
-I was just so excited to see you.
- 황당하군요
- 당신을 잃고 싶지 않아요
-This is too weird.
-No, it's not. I don't wanna lose you.
우술라가 당신인 줄 알고
잠자리를...
It's like I was saying to Ursula
when I was making love..
너무 황당해요
Yeah. It's too weird.
이제 끝이군요
So I guess this is it.
그래요
Yeah.
서로에게 잘된 일이에요
Maybe it's for the best.
- 언니의 냄새가 나요
- 당신도요
-You smell just like her.
-Yeah, so do you.
- 왜 이래요?
- 기대고 있어요
-What are you doing?
-I'm leaning.
내가 종종 기대는 곳이죠
This is where I lean.
그렇군요
Okay.
- 브렌다, 벌이에요!
- 뭐라고요?
-Brenda, a bee!
-What?
옷 속으로 벌이 들어갔으니
쏘이기 전에 벗어요
It's flown into your blouse, and you better
undo your buttons lest it sting you.
- 왜 이러는지 알겠어요
- 그래요?
-I think I know what's going on here.
-You do?
부인이 레스비언이라서
당신도 힘들 테지만
Look, I know it must be hard
that your wife is a lesbian..
유부남이 이러면 안 돼요
but it's wrong. You're married.
- 잘 알겠어요
- 다행이군요
-I totally understand.
-Okay, good.
브라 좀 보면 안 돼요?
Could I just see your bra?
안녕
Hi.
- 그 바지는 어디서 났어?
- 네가 줬잖아
-Where'd you get those jeans?
-You gave them to me.
- 내가 언제?
- 사실은 내가 가져갔어
-No, I didn't!
-All right, I took them.
잉크 자국이 있어서
괜찮을 줄 알았어
I figured it'd be okay because
you've got a big ink stain on the crotch.
- 내 브라도 가져갔어?
- 브라라니?
-Oh, no! Did you take my bra too?
-What bra?
- 분홍색 꽃무늬
- 네가 지금 입은 것?
-The pink one with the flowers.
-You mean the one you're wearing?
관두겠어요!
I quit!
기대한 대로군
Sounds about right.
이게 뭐야?
What is this?
이해를 돕기 위한 거야
This is just to give you an idea.
칸막이를 설치해서
아기의 사생활을 지켜 주고
We can put screens here
so that the baby has privacy..
천장엔 움직이는 장난감을
매달고
and maybe a mobile over the crib..
이건 아기가 태어나기 전까지
무전기로 쓰면 돼
and here's a baby monitor which, till the
baby comes, we can use as walkie-talkies.
근사해!
You're so sweet!
맙소사! 아기에게
헉시를 선물로 줬구나
Oh, my God!
And you gave the baby Hugsy!
아기를 둘 위치를
표시한 거야
That's really just to show
where the baby would go.
오해의 여지가 있으니
들고 있을게
Why don't I hold on to him
so there's no confusion.
조이, 아기가 울면
무척 시끄러울 거야
Joey, the baby is gonna be crying.
It's gonna be loud.
- 나도 시끄럽잖아
- 밤새 자지도 않아
-I'm loud.
-It's gonna be up all night.
- 나도 그래
- 토하기도 하고
-I'm up all night.
-It's gonna poop.
이하동문!
Hello!
네 여자들은 어쩌고?
What about all the women?
데리고 온 여자가
아기를 싫어하면
If I'm bringing home a woman
who can't stand a baby..
그런 여자는 만나기 싫어
then maybe I don't wanna
be with that woman.
나이트클럽 화장실에서
해도 돼
Or maybe we'll do it
in the bathroom of the club!
아기 앞에서 이런 말은
안 꺼낼게
But I won't say stuff
like that around the baby.
진심이야?
Joey, are you sure?
힘들 때도 있을 테지만...
Yeah. Look, I know sometimes
it'll be hard, okay..
정말 좋을 거야
but it'll also be really,
really great.
레이첼, 정말 네가
안갔으면 좋겠어
Please, Rachel,
I really want you to stay.
나도 여기 있고 싶어
고마워
I want me to stay too. Thank you.
- 조이, 침대가 귀엽다
- 응, 길에서 주웠어
-Joey, look at this crib. It's so cute.
-I know. I found it on the street.
뭐? 정말?
상태가 쓸 만하군
Are you..? Really?
This is in such good condition.
저게 뭐야?
Whoa! What's under the cover?
- 글쎄
- 움직이잖아
-I don't know.
-It's moving.
꼬리가 달렸어, 버려!
It's got a tail! Get it out of here!
알았어
Okay!
'펄 하몬을 기리며'
부인은 돌아가셨어
어떻게 아냐고?
Well, the old lady died.
And how do I know?
그녀의 마지막 소원이
마지막 키스였어
Because her dying wish
was for one last kiss.
내가 힘이 세니까...
And because I'm such a strong,
strapping alleenstaande..
로비까지 업어야 했어
I had to carry her body to the lobby.
결코 가볍지 않았다고
You know, and she was
not a slight woman.
그래도 네가 그 집을
얻게 됐잖아, 야호!
But I don't care, because
you got the apartment. Yes!
이사를 가지 않고
여기 계속 살기로 했어
Yeah. I think I'm gonna stay here.
정말 다행이지?
Isn't that great?
뭐? 너희는 정말...
What..? You..
But.. Bu..